<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tamanna Kaur</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tamanna Kaur</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rosetta Stone for R and Python</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/09/what-s-poppin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/09/what-s-poppin/</guid>
      <description>Let’s talk about R and Python! Some background information based completely off what I know/remember:
Python is one of the most user friendly coding languages that exist, it was actually named after the movie monty python and the holy grail (hilarious movie, 10/10 recommend). Also made fairly recently, 1990s I believe (#90skids).
R is for really for science nerds. Like myself and probably you, since you’re reading a R-coded website right now :) But it is also pretty neat if I say so myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Data Wrangling and Data Exploration ###Introduction!!!!
I chose to datasets that focused on different countries’ statistics. The reason I chose these datasets is because I thought it would be really interesting to see the correlation different aspects of countries globally rather than just picking something that was in one specific area and based off one specific culture, to be able to see universal trends. So my data set under CP came from the UN data website which has collected from more than 20 International statistical sources that compiled regularly by the statistics and population divisions of the United Nations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling  0. (5 pts) Introduce your dataset and each of your variables (or just your main variables if you have lots) in a paragraph. What are they measuring? How many observations?  library(readxl) Affairs &amp;lt;- read_excel(&amp;quot;Affairs.xlsx&amp;quot;) #View(Affairs) ***Hello! My dataset is a cross-section data of married people from a survey conducted by Psychology Today in 1969. It was about extramarital affairs, but the amount of factos allows for lots of correlations to be tested of married people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
